When you upload your audio, we switch
from no audio because we got some audio
into a pending state. And from this
pending state,
Chrome is able to figure out that this
is something that he should focus on and
he should uh process those. We can also
get some errors. Uh we can have no
audio. Somehow audio wasn't uploaded.
Then well, we can't transcribe call when
we don't have any any voice available.
Also you see this too long to process
and you might ask okay so if I go over
those 4 minutes I will have no
transcription. No it's just um well
there is a certain limit. Uh we made
sure that you can transcribe our long
conversations with current um with with
current limits. However if you well if
you open your
uh if you call somebody all day long you
probably reach those limits. And for
that we have an extra state.
Then background worker picks up uh call
in the pending state switches the state
to cued and this way it will notify
other background workers that right now
are not there but user can possibly
create an extra chrome that is also
tasked with processing.
This way when first chrome is picking up
some job it switches its state and locks
all the other crrons from uh trying to
process the same call. So we are
preventing some race conditions which we
do not expect at the moment is just some
defensive programming
and finally all the background worker is
doing all the calls is asking open AI to
transcribe the audio. it's getting the
transcription. If it gets the
transcription, it ask for summary and it
can also run into some errors. Open AI
cannot can become unavailable and then
yeah unfortunately we cannot do anything
about it uh unless we start running our
own models.
>> And that brings us to the topic of uh
yeah our features are very young. We
started our team like four months ago.
>> Yeah. in January.
>> Yes. So
>> all the features are very young and we
are expecting from you some kind of
feedback, preferably a lot of feedback
so we know where to focus. One of the
concerns that is appearing constantly is
privacy. So tell us if you would like us
to run our models on premise. Do not
send any uh code data to OpenAI. do not
send any call data to uh to to Google or
maybe you would like some options to
have your own voice models.
uh maybe a little bit about the UI and
then I'll
>> yeah uh about the voice transcription as
as I said with the current version of
the transcription
you have a less reactive feedback of the
UI and so it would be mainly be like
some UI improvement to make the thing
more snappy more reactive and also
improve the quality of the transcription
because it all can also happen since AI
models are not perfect that you would
have some snippets of transcription that
are really accurate with what you you
have said and so we also would like to
improve in the quality of these and
maybe in the future which is maybe not
related to transcription directly but
may the introduction of voice command
would be something that uh we thought of
as well for these uh these kind of
features but uh it's still yeah we still
have to to know what people would be
interested in and so it's important for
us to have feedbacks about those if you
if you have features you would like so
yeah
>> voice commands can be especially
interesting when if you attended the
previous talk about NLP about uh aski
imagine that instead of typing the whole
command, hey, show me uh my top
employees, you just press and hold some
button responsible for uh for voice
typing and there you go in 3 seconds.
Very lazy uh type of operation, huh?
>> Yeah. uh some more quirks um some more
improvements related to VIP and uh also
discuss we can als that's let me let me
quickly
tease you what's on the table we could
do something called semantic search
imaged
that you have a lot of calls with
current implementation of UDO It's very
difficult to search through million of
rows of text
and above that it's difficult to find
something because you need to type
exactly the phrase that you put in
there. Then uh what I'm proposing in
here what we could do is we could
introduce semantic search. We already
have tools for that with uh well with
birth of AI module. We already have
tools to introduce semantic search where
you would roughly describe what you want
to find like here latest sales
functionality should find viewing new
sales feature in the sales funnel. It's
not a direct march. It's not a keyword
search. It's roughly grabs the concept
the idea the semantic meaning of your
query and finds all all the codes that
uh that are similar. That's something on
the table.
Another thing that we could introduce is
co analysis that is already present in
the industry. And what is specifically
interesting to me is something called
moments. So you all probably heard of u
of sentiment analysis, right? So we can
tell you okay you have five calls that
are positive, five that are me and two
that are negative. That is in my opinion
uh
not very
uh interesting information. Much rather
would you probably like to know which
parts of the conversation answer certain
question. And this is where moments come
into play because we can have AI scan
the whole transcript and then highlight
all the all the parts that answer your
question negatively and answer your
question in a positive way. Then you can
count those and you can have more
more snappy feeling of if uh more more
realistic feeling of what the call
represents. Was was it something that
you have to focus about? That's
something that we can introduce very
quickly. Let us know if that's something
interesting to you. And yeah, last thing
is uh the discuss integration. I don't
know how many people here use discus.
There are some discus user. That's good
to know. Yeah. Let me know if you would
also like to see transcriptions in
there. uh depending on the feedback that
we get from you we will um we will put
our focus accordingly and I guess it's a
time for question we have a lot of time
for questions so we are all yours
>> you can uh open that up you have our
slides in there
do we have somebody All right
>> so thank you Dylan thank you Andre for
this great talk so let's go to the Q&A
session
So you can ask your question by the
through the QR code and I will ask the
first question then. So the first one is
is a Swiss German supported by the real
time like any language that you can
enable on your audio database is
supported by the transcription uh by
transcription snip. Yes. So if it's
available yes it is uh
>> I don't know specific yeah Swiss German
is a little bit specific language maybe
>> but if if whisper if open AI supports it
we support it. Yeah,
>> we don't have specific models to to
handle them.
>> Okay, thank you very much. So the second
question is in case of offline meetings,
is it possible to upload MP3 file
instead of realtime transcription
>> currently? No, not with the
transcription snippet. You cannot upload
the MP3 file.
>> Okay,
>> thank you very much. The third question
is will odo get all functionalities
funded in ringover?
>> I couldn't hear you. Sorry. So the third
question is will odo get all the
functionalities founded in ringover?
>> I'm not familiar with that feature. What
what features can can they move the
question to the to the bottom and
specify exact features?
>> Okay. Okay. I'll I'll go to the next
question. So is it possible in
collaboration modes to identify person
that speak and add name beside the
transcription text?
>> Uh currently no. And it's also the
limitation of like maybe the VIP calls
is that the models that are used for the
transcription are not meant to identify
people that are speaking uh as we are
using them and so no it's not uh really
some something right now here.
>> However, it's something that we can
bring to VIP calls a little bit faster
if you want that because we have two
streams of audio. So it's easy in VIP
calls. It's easier in VIP calls than uh
in the live dictation
>> because here Yeah. in the live dictation
basically how it works is that you have
it's meant to have like one microphone
recording in every and it's picking up
every sound and so in your meeting you
you won't really be able to identify
people with that at least not easily.
>> But that's a good question. Thank you
for that question.
>> Thank you. Yes. So let's go to the next
question. Will the transcription work
with multiple languages? Switch within
the text.
>> Like if you want to switch like if you
want to switch while recording, you
cannot because the session has been has
to have has to be created with a
specific language. Uh so you would have
to stop the recording, start again,
record in another language. So it might
be a limitation here. However, even if
your language uh you selected another
language, but you start to speak, for
example, if you if you selected English
and you start speaking in French, for
example, the model will still pick up
what you're saying and most of the time
it will either do a proper transcription
or it will translate the transcription
in the in the language that is set up.
So, it could work.
>> We did a couple of tests also in VIP for
example whereas you have whole context
of the whole conversation at once. There
is no uh language setup. The model will
figure out the language and uh yeah
according to the tests we perform it
handles all the languages that we are
speaking in our team.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Thank you very much. So the next
question is how long will the audio
recordings be stored?
That is something also that we really
want to get your feedback on because
retention policy I know that's something
that you would like to probably uh have
options to set and we plan to just add
it in settings uh just a simple select
selector so you can um you can you can
select that time yourself
and yeah that's that's it that's
something also we need to get your
feedback on currently currently they are
stored indefinitely.
Okay. So the next question is does it
work with air?
>> Does it work with with what?
>> Does it work with air call? So I guess
it's a a very
>> I guess they are talking about one of
the providers
and
it's huh that's a nice thing about